Hey! This time!
We are in a place rich in nature!
Did the fishing come true right away?
Yes, indeed!
I've always wanted to fish with the members.
Just the two of us, like this assistant.
It looks like, you know...
It's shallow. Is that why you call it thin? Shallow?
It's shallow!
It's very deep.
The river?
The depth of the river.
Well, it started out so slow...
We're in such a natural place.
Equal to... This time...
I'd like to have a relaxing camping trip.
Thank you very much!
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
It's okay, kali.
Wait, wait, wait, are you waiting? Come here.
Waiting for you. Are you in?
It's in.
Okay, so we're gonna explore a little bit, but...
Shall we go down to the river? It's just down here.
The river was said to be shallow at the opening.
It's a little more like camping.
Yes, it is. Look at this.
The view is amazing.
I'm taking pictures of the view! I'm taking pictures of the view!
It's a perfect camp view area today.
It's a beautiful day here today.
Beautiful!
It's cold!
How is it?
It's nice.
I've never heard of a dry river. I've never heard of drying a river before.
I've never heard of it.
There's a river, too.
There are barbecue facilities on the river.
I'll let you touch the water once, Kaname.
I'll hold it. I'm filming outside.
No problem. We're not playing in the river anymore.
Hey...
It's great!
It's nice.
It's good.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to touch it.
Okay.
It's tight. It's hard to do.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
He's concerned about it.
It's that one, isn't it?
What?
Help him quickly.
Help him quickly!
I'll do it.
They're both for outside use.
This is for outside.
What?
This is for outside use.
I'm making them both fake right now.
It's so hard, so hard, so hard
I'm laughing so hard
Blue sky is terrible
Blue sky is terrible!
Takato Okura
Here it is!
I'll touch the water.
Camera one is OK?
Camera one is clear.
Is this the first camera? Is this the first camera?
Two's OK.
Wow, it's so cold!
With this sky.
This clarity.
Come a little closer to the camera.
Here you go.
This transparency.
Oh, it's so close!
Oh, this way.
This transparency, ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, my.
That's fantastic.
These outfits, the three of you.
It's so inconsistent with the season.
It's just a craft.
But it's enough to get you through today.
Yes.
Shall we go to the forest?
What do you mean, to the woods?
Oh, we're going deeper and deeper.
Let's go up a little bit.
Okay.
I like it. Nature. I've always wanted to come here.
You'll drop me soon.
No, no, no, no.
It's going to be a fun, beautiful day.
Amazing! Don't go any further!
So cute!
He's back.
I can feel the oxygen.
He's rigid.
You're good at it.
There are so many trees.
It's like a road to another world.
It's good. You're good.
Here we go.
Gonzak Warrior.
We'll go after them. Let's go after them.
What kind of race is this?
Oh, no. It's got a lot of soot on it.
We're probably out of carbon dioxide.
Is it oxygen? Nothing but oxygen.
I mean, this is such a nice space.
This is amazing.
This place is like...
It looks like a place to play with nature.
You know, just playing with nature.
Something you can only do at a camp.
It's so beautiful.
We can do all kinds of things here today.
There's a river.
And I'd love to eat some good food.
That's nice.
Let's all...
Let's get some air.
Yeah.
Let's go.
Okay, then.
After I breathe in this negative ion air.
I'm going to see how good I look in the air.
Okay. - Okay.
That's good.
Wow, this is hard.
Breathe in this air and you'll be in a commercial.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
I'm going to manage the air so that I can sell it.
That's right.
Who wants to go first?
Let's do the canned air championship.
The canned air championship. Air Canning Championship
Okay, let's go to the top of the list.
Oh!
I knew it.
They'll be on later.
I'll start with a profile.
Then I'll ask you to inhale and exhale all at once.
And then exhale.
And then I'll say a few words to the camera.
Yes, sir.
Here we go. All right.
Here we go.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
There's a diet called "phew".
It's a diet that used to be popular.
Shall we go?
Let's go!
Here we go.
Yum.
Yay, okay!
Okay, now, this is the standard.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What?
I mean...
Shhhhhhhhh!
WOW!
It's like China or something, it's a big pole.
It's constitutional, the way you breathe.
No, that was good.
Kanae-san, shall we go?
This is the standard.
Let's get started!
The air is definitely right.
We're going to commercial!
We're going to commercial! Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on!
They're doing it so well next to me.
Let's go, Mr. Takada!
Let's go next, Mr. Takada! Let's go next, Mr. Takada.
Hmm? Hmm? Hmm?
Oh, it's a selfie.
This is so hard!
It's so hard.
It's so hard!
Shall we do it? A chilling party for Takato's airy feeling?
Yes, sir.
What do you think?
Wow!
Nature is amazing!
Phew!
Phew.
Huh.
Like a comedian.
Phew!
There's something like this, isn't there?
Who decides?
There are comedians who say it this way.
Okay, well, I...
I... I don't know...
To the better of the two of you.
Well...
Yes...
I'm going to go make an offer for the commercial.
Okay, um...
Audition, let's go after the audition.
Let's go after the audition.
Let's say you're coming home from an audition.
Then, can I ask you to walk from here?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, no.
How was your audition today?
Maybe I did a little better, but I think I did pretty well.
Thank you for earlier. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
I'm from Okura Water Company.
Mr. Okura, the water company.
I auditioned for the face of this delicious air.
We got the results at the meeting.
I'm looking forward to it.
From Stardust Promotion.
Oh, yeah?
I know who he is.
Then let me choose one.
Yes, please.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
One moment, please.
I'll take it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you very much.
Here they come.
I'll be on the one that fell.
Please.
If you use curry, you can't sell the product.
Is that so?
Maybe it's the water that builds muscle.
No, no, no.
It's not air.
Maybe we sell water that builds muscle.
That's true.
What are we doing here in nature?
It's true.
It's so big and natural.
It's like, this much nature.
The air is really good.
Well, I'm going back.
That's about it for today.
What was that?
He just tried to kill me.
What are you doing feeling nature?
Oh...
That's just the beginning. That's the stage we're at.
First you said "Yuru-Can.
I said, "Let's go to YuruCan.
First of all, what are we going to do?
What do you mean by "Yuru-Camp"?
I said, "Camping.
Well, you set up a tent, pitch a tent...
Staying overnight...
That's what camping is all about, right?
You don't have to do that.
Come to nature for a day trip
Let's enjoy what we can do at camp.
Let's enjoy things that can only be enjoyed in nature.
Let's do the things we can do in loose camping.
that we can do at loose-camping.
What is it, for example?
Okay, I'll make an announcement first.
After today...
We're going to have a barbecue.
Barbecue BBQ!
We'll do it all day long.
Let's enjoy the rest of the day with these three.
Let's have fun!
Let's go for it!
Let's eat meat!
Let's go for it.
We're going to have a barbecue.
First of all, let's cut vegetables.
Cutting vegetables
They're pretty thick.
It's very thick.
There's a difference between barbecuing in the city and barbecuing
and barbecue in a natural setting
I'm going to do it at a convenience store.
It's different, isn't it?
I haven't eaten it yet.
Shiitake mushrooms are delicious.
They're really good! They're really good!